<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Orchid Care</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">close</string>

    <string name="catasetum">Catasetum</string>
    <string name="catasetum_desc">This unusual group of orchids offer
        s fascinating, waxy flowers that often have the peculiar habi
        t of discharging their pollen masses (pollinia) onto pollinat
        ors. Almost always deciduous, the pseudobulbous plants have s
        trict growing and resting periods. Most flower before enterin
        g a dormant period when they drop their leaves.
</string>

    <string name="dendrobium">Dendrobium</string>
    <string name="dendrobium_desc">Dendrobium is a diverse genus of o
        rchids with different cultural needs. Many go through a growt
        h phase and then a rest phase during the course of one year,
        and must be given water and temperature to match these period
        s of growth and rest. Flowers can last one day to many weeks,
        depending on the type. Owing to the extreme diversity of the
        genus, we have categorized culture according to the following
        main types:
</string>

    <string name="miltonia">Miltonia</string>
    <string name="miltonia_desc">These striking orchids, which are al
        so known as pansy orchids, owing to their similarity to garde
        n pansies, are enjoying increasing popularity. Miltoniopsis a
        re cool-growing orchids that originate in the higher elevation
        s of the Andes in Colombia, Panama and Ecuador. The warmer-gr
        owing species, properly miltonias, originate from the Minas G
        erais area of Brazil and more closely resemble large-flowered
        oncidiums. Their flowers can be brilliantly patterned.
</string>

    <string name="novice_dendrobium">Novice Dendrobium</string>
    <string name="novice_dendrobium_desc">Dendrobium is a diverse gen
        us of orchids with different cultural needs. This culture inf
        ormation is for the phalenopsis-type dendrobiums pictured abo
        ve. They are evergreen with thin, tall stems (pseudobulbs).
</string>

    <string name="odontoglossum">Odontoglossum</string>
    <string name="odontoglossum_desc">These high-altitude orchids fro
        m the New World Tropics flourish where cool temperatures prev
        ail year round. Odontoglossums are known for their striking s
        prays of flowers. Culture is similar for hybrids in this grou
        p, some being Odontonia, Odontioda and Vuylstekeara.
</string>

    <string name="phalaenopsis">Phalaenopsis</string>
    <string name="phalaenopsis_desc">Phalaenopsis, the moth orchid, i
        s perhaps the best orchid for growing in the home, and is als
        o a favorite with greenhouse growers. Well-grown plants can f
        lower often, sometimes with a few flowers throughout the year
        , though the main season is late winter into spring. Average
        home temperatures and conditions are usually sufficient. Flow
        er stems on certain hybrids can be forced to rebloom by cutti
        ng the tip off after the initial flowering. Only healthy plan
        ts should be induced to flower repeatedly. Culture for Doriti
        s, a related genus, thought by some to be conspecific with Ph
        alaenopsis, and Doritaenopsis, a hybrid between the two gener
        a, is the same as for pure Phalaenopsis.
</string>

    <string name="vanda">Vanda</string>
    <string name="vanda_desc">The Vanda Alliance is made up mostly of
        warm- and full-sun-growing orchids with colorful flowers. Ori
        ginating in tropical Asia, they are easily grown in warm clim
        ates, where plants are cultivated outside in light shade, suc
        h as in a lath house. In climates where winters are cold, the
        y are often summered outside, and grown inside during the win
        ter in a sunny window, or year round in a greenhouse. Smaller
        growing ascocendas are best outside tropical conditions.
</string>

    <string name="about_text">This app gives you, the user, an overvi
        ew of what an orchid plant is.  The Home tab gives you a brie
        fly description, the Search tab let you search through the di
        fferent orchids covered in this app and then see their info.
        The Add Orchid tab lets you create a reminder stored in a dat
        abase that will prompt you with the name of your orchid, filt
        er down to its type and the selection of a date to start the
        guidance to its maintenance and finally the My Grove tab let
        you see how many reminders you have created in the Add Orchid
        tab.</string>

    <string name="copyrights">App Made by: Saudeep - Copyrights 2016</string>

    <string name="home_desc">Welcome to the fascinating world of
        Orchids.  Orchids have a large variety of flowers, which you
        can
        enjoy from seeing it to take care of them.  They will bring
        you happiness and entertainment.</string>
</resources>